I've just been to a place that has a pop and catchy feel to it.
Watch out, watch out, I just forgot about that.
I'm so easy to forget, aren't I?
So, here it is.
Exactly the same!
What's it called again?
It's called "something road".
It's an underground street in Ikebukuro.
It's very convenient.
You can go from the west exit right next to the station to the east exit at once.
It's very easy. It comes out at Parcon.
It's very fast.
And this is the other thing... that you gave me a while ago.
Let's see...
I think this is it.
Specialty product. Yokohama City, Kanagawa Ward.
It's a booboo.
Let's see if it looks like something bossy, but it's not.
That's right, that picture Mariko brings, the one that looks like a dog, that's actually not her!
She's sitting on a chair like this, looking over there.
Then, she's like a black HAMAKI, HAMAKI, HAMAKI, HAMAKI...
And like this... ah... brandy, I know...
By the way, I was sent here to find out where I am, and I think it would be very easy for a company-loving master to find out.
I'm sure it's a place I've seen many times before.
The Yokosuka Line, the Tokaido Line, the Yokohama Line, the Keihin-Tohoku Line, and the Tokaido Line.
Yokohama Line, Keihin-Tohoku Line and Keikyu Line are all running side by side.
There's only one place like this.
There is only one such place, Aokibashi Bridge, right above here.
It's so close to Yokohama Station that it's not impossible to walk there.
It's a nice place.
Aoki-bashi bridge is here, right?
It's like this.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no...
I did it last week... with low tension.
The players have to be more enthusiastic.
No, no, no... that's the second time you've introduced the master, isn't it?
No, I feel a little guilty.
Don't do it twice.
You didn't do the "this is the place to be" thing.
Well, well, well...
This is both our fault.
You're right, you're right, you're right.
That's why...
If you like trains, you'll love the Aokibashi bridge.
On the other hand...
On the other hand, the person who came here didn't see a train, so I thought it would be better to see a train with a train.
So it's pretty rare... not that it's rare... but there are 7 trains coming one after the other.
It's great.
I wonder why I'm not good at this kind of thing.
I explained why it's your first time.
I explained the "Where are we now?" combo.
I'm surprised, I'm surprised, I'm surprised, I'm surprised, I'm surprised, in so many ways...
I'm so surprised...
And there's one more thing...
I thought the current photo was taken there, but when I actually went there, I found it to be here.
I see... there it is... and that area... there it is!
8... 8... 8...
I wonder... Tricolor...
Zama City, Kanagawa Prefecture.
This time, it's in Yokohama City.
It's in Yokohama. Well, it's a little bit like an intersection.
It looks like an intersection, but it's a little slippery.
If there is something here under the elevated railway tracks, it means there is something going up, probably a pedestrian bridge.
It's probably a pedestrian bridge.
I wonder how many times I've been here.
There is a place called Tsurumi in Yokohama.
There is a pedestrian bridge connecting Keikyu Tsurumi and JR Tsurumi in Yokohama.
There's a pedestrian bridge.
I've seen this view many times.
Here we go.
Show!
Wow! Nice!
Not so much.
What? That's not what you meant?
What do you call it? Aah! Just like that.
I see.
You surprised me. I was surprised at you.
No, you weren't.
It's okay. It's okay.
It's okay.
Like this.
This is JR Tsurumi.
And Keikyu Tsurumi's in the foreground.
This pedestrian bridge goes all the way over here.
From here...
Probably... well, I mean, he passed by.
You took this picture, didn't you? You're good at giving hints, aren't you?
Yes, the color of the pedestrian bridge, too, you know, the one in Machida, Ayaka, that we did last week?
I didn't have time to go there, but I found it on Solidview. Like, "Oh, here it is!
That was a good clue. - Very good.
What's the north entrance?
North? North? It's not a prosperous area, but if you look at the map on Street View, you'll see it's under the railroad tracks and...
Is that it? That's right.
That's right. I can't get over it. That was fun.
I'll be back soon.
I'll be there as long as I can.
Yes, I'm live now.
Greetings. We're live!
Hello.
Good evening.
This is how we'll be doing today.
Thank you very much.
Are you tired?
Are you okay?
It's a little bit messy.
What's going on?
How's it going? Live delivery
What do you think? How's today's live transmission?
Well, it's been, what, three months? About three months.
Can you do it?
Devil's advocate... yes... let's enjoy it.
Not good, not bad... not bad, not bad... not bad... not bad... not bad... not bad... not bad... not bad...
Okay, let's proceed with the recording.
So... ramen's so irresistible, especially this time of year.
Can't get enough of it?
It's been too hot this summer, but that's okay... to replenish salt.
It's delicious, but ramen's the most exciting thing.
When it gets a little cold, that's for sure.
I'm going to try it and do it on my own.
Please apologize. It's Shirousuke's story.
So...
Ramen rashers... Ramen rashers! This show is full of rashers.
But if I introduce them, it'll sound like a ramen show, so I've refrained from doing so.
But this time of year, it can't be helped.
What? I love Kyushu's tonkotsu (pork bone) ramen, and I even run a study group called the Kyu-tou-zone.
I'd like to introduce to you the ramen from the holy land of Kyushu's tonkotsu ramen.
Since it's from a sacred place, I think it's a good idea to give it a try.
Kyushu Tokkotsu Ramen Study Group
Enjoy!
Kido
Kido!
So, shall we go?
Why are you crying?
I'm so moved.
It's been a while.
That's why you're so great, Richard.
Thank you very much.
Chuo-ku, Tokyo
First of all, I'd like to say that I'm very impressed with your e-mail form.
Address...
5. age, gender, etc.
5 occupation
This is not a question at all.
You can write your real job.
Of course, you can write anything you want.
I'd like to know what you're into.
Like, you know, you like Subie...
There are people like that.
This person is a member of the Ebichu family, of course.
He is also a member of Kyushu Tonkotsu Ramen Study Group
Oh my...
Anyone can come to our study group.
I see...
You are also free to leave.
Daily 11 is a pain in the ass... something weird... something that doesn't say "Are you sure you want to do this?
I'm not sure why you're stopping. I thought it was a texting relationship.
I'm not sure if it's a good idea or not, but I'm sure it's a good idea.
Mr. Sarpong, the shrimp's part-time worker...
I'm Bill, from Kurume City, Fukuoka Prefecture.
I had tonkotsu ramen in Kurume, Fukuoka Prefecture!
The hardness is, of course, "crunchy"!
So, what a surprise!
There are many theories about Kurume, but one of the most popular is...
There is a Kyushu ramen called "Hakata no Ramen" nowadays, you know?
Kurume is said to be the birthplace of that.
I've been to Kurume several times.
I've been to Kurume several times, and the food stalls and stores are of the highest caliber.
I'm going to take a picture now, is that okay?
It's really amazing... who's that?
I saw it recently and thought it was the most amazing among all of them
I'm downloading it!
I'm in the middle of a downloading roller coaster, right?
I don't even know a girl.
I don't know why you do it... where you go, where you get into it, where you go crazy... but, you know... we're after dinner.
So it's not so bad, is it?
Yeah.
I think so.
I think it's a plane.
So if you're going to Kurume, you can probably go to Hakata Fukuoka Airport and go there too.
I'd probably go to Hakata Fukuoka Airport, then transfer to a jr. train, but it'd take at least 30 minutes to get to the airport.
I'm not good at 340 minutes from Hakata... so I'll just take the smart way...
I really love this ramen.
I was really convinced that I really like this Kyushu Tonkotsu this summer.
So it's like meeting the girl of my dreams.
I wrote this too, but most of Kurume's tonkotsu ramen has a thick soup, but this ramen has a fried egg with pork oil on top.
But this ramen here is topped with a fried egg of pork oil.
It's delicious!
It's quite rich, but that's what makes it so addictive.
Yes, it's true... this is good richness.
What is he talking about?
There's a guilty conscience.
Well, well, well...
That's what I'm saying.
It's a little too much, isn't it?
That's right.
One thing...
I've met my ideal type.
That's right.
I didn't know there were girls like her.
I wonder why we're from Tokyo.
Why do you think we're from Tokyo?
What do you mean?
Because we can eat in Kurume.
I wish I was born in Kurume.
If they were in Tokyo, we wouldn't be able to see them.
That's true, but...
But maybe...
It's because I was here.
I had a lot of opportunities because I was here.
I see.
Maybe we can meet.
I'll have to go.
I think Krumé is great.
Of course. The ramen is amazing.
But...
You know those food stalls in Nakasu?
That kind of thing.
They're all over the streets of Krume.
They're amazing!
There are so many yakitori restaurants.
They are very delicious.
I see.
Yes, it's like the old shopping streets of Kurume.
It's a great town.
The town's so nice.
I really want to hear it! I want to hear it, Natural!
Well, well, well... speaking of ramen...
Speaking of ramen, I ate some yesterday.
I ate a little ramen yesterday.
It's miso ramen. It's on top of the ramen.
It's a little bit different from ordinary miso ramen.
It's a little different from the usual miso ramen, but it's good, too, but it's been a long time since I've had it.
This is the one that's hidden in the bowl.
When it's in there, it makes you happy, like Shippuden
It's nice when it comes out like this, isn't it?
It's a rare character, so it's surprising that it's not included nowadays.
It's a rare character, so it's surprising that it's not included now.
I'm sure you're right, I wish they'd include it because it would be lucky if they did.
It's the whirlpool of Naruto in Tokushima.
It's called Naruto's whirlpool.
I've been calling myself Naruto for a long time.
I've been saying to my mother, "What is it?" and she says, "Oh, it's true, it's a 'no,' isn't it?
So I told her I was happy for her.
って言ってなるほど 確かにまあこうで今ちょっとこれあれだけどですね逆さまに回転させると
I see... well... well... well... well... well... well... well... it's delicious...
By the way, when it comes to ramen, what do you think is the first thing you should do?
I'm from Kyushu, and I think that's the best... but... everyone has their own tastes.
I like Tonkotsu-kotsu too. I like the light Tonkotsu-kotsu type too.
Shoyu Tonkotsu-kiten, I guess.
By the way, I'm in a craze for "Abu-Soba" (oil noodles) "Abu-Soba" (oil noodles) "Abu-Soba" (oil noodles) "Abu-Soba" (oil noodles)
Mayonnaise!
I'm going to start eating mayonnaise.
Once you start eating it, you know...
I heard that oil soba originated from a restaurant in Mitaka City, my hometown in Tokyo.
It started there, and at first we were told that there was an elder sister ramen in the soup.
We went there, but we didn't know how to eat it, and suddenly there was only noodles in a bowl.
I asked the people around me how to eat it, and they told me to put vinegar, raayu and soy sauce and mix it by myself.
It was shocking, and now I know it's become a citizen's dish.
I've never seen anything like it back then.
I miss Chintin-tei, that's what it was called.
It's just in the comments.
Musashi Sakai's the birthplace of abura soba.
It says "Chinchin-tei".
I wonder if it's still there.
That's the birthplace of aburasoba.
I'll have to go there.
Ramen's good for a lot of things.
I'm so happy.
Especially this time of year.
It's cold.
I get a runny nose when I eat things, not just ramen.
The warmth helps.
I don't care if it's good ramen at a ramen shop.
I'm eating ramen, and I'm thinking, "Oh no, oh no, oh no, oh no!
But if there's no tissue in front of you, your score goes down.
Oh, they don't understand.
If there's a tissue in front of you, you're like, "I'm going to go to this restaurant again.
Sometimes they're in the wrong place, like under the hand blues.
I'm sure there are times when you have to put them in a space like this...
I wonder if it's like this...
Let's see... let's see... wait a minute...
Wait a minute, there's one more.
Yes, I have another one.
Rasha?
Rasha, wow, this one, too...
May I? Yes, sir.
May I? Excuse me, gentlemen.
I'm sorry. This one's great, too.
This is also amazing. - Special Mission Specialist Nekotoku Uniya, Isogo-ku, Yokohama.
Oh, uh...
The other day...
The other day, the first Ultraman and Kamen Rider #1, Sanma, Fuji Fujioka, Hiroshi... had a talk.
It's a great event.
A great event! A drop of water in Shimokitazawa!
So I went to Shimokitazawa.
So I went to Shimokitazawa to get something to eat.
I heard there's a restaurant called Tori Soba Salt.
I'm Rasha, by the way.
Can I see your picture?
Let's do it now!
What if it's in the downstairs?
How often do they show up in the "down"?
And that's why...
Salt ramen.
Maybe that's it.
I'm sure you've all been there before.
It's so intense!
The approval is that approval, right?